【The fate that cannot be liberated】
[해방될 수 없는 운명]
[relation]
[관계]
You stay up late reading.
당신은 늦게까지 책을 읽습니다.
Where are you going now?
지금 어디로 가시나요?
I want to take a look
한번 살펴보고 싶어요
if story
이야기라면
it is true.
그건 진실이야.
Take a break before leaving.
떠나기 전에 잠시 휴식을 취하세요.
Your Majesty, it's time to take your medicine.
폐하, 이제 약을 드실 시간입니다.
after I die,
내가 죽은 후에,
If I am not buried in the Rong family cemetery
내가 롱씨네 묘지에 묻히지 않았다면
Will they blame me?
그들이 나를 비난할까요?
Master, his old injury has not fully recovered yet.
스승님, 그의 오래된 부상은 아직 완전히 회복되지 않았습니다.
everything will get better.
모든 것이 좋아질 것입니다.
My old wounds.
내 오래된 상처.
They are very serious.
그들은 매우 심각합니다.
Why am I healed?
나는 왜 치유되는가?
Madam always has
부인은 항상 그랬어요
Rare treasures that we don’t know about.
우리가 모르는 희귀한 보물.
He knows ways that we don’t.
그분은 우리가 모르는 방법을 알고 계십니다.
She had successfully healed him before.
그녀는 이전에 그를 성공적으로 치료한 적이 있었습니다.
it's not surprising
그것은 놀라운 일이 아니다
May she heal you again.
그녀가 당신을 다시 치료해주기를 바랍니다.
Master.
주인.
teacher.
선생님.
There is a painter named Huang here.
여기 황이라는 화가가 있어요.
He said he was your friend.
그는 당신의 친구라고 말했습니다.
He wanted to see her outside.
그는 그녀를 밖에서 보고 싶었습니다.
Mother.
어머니.
I'm going to tell you something.
나는 당신에게 뭔가를 말할 것입니다.
Gui's mother.
구이의 어머니.
Multiple sclerosis. Jiu.
다발성 경화증. 지우.
I'm playing chicken here.
저는 여기서 치킨놀이를 하고 있어요.
How about these two?
이 둘은 어때요?
Sorry, miss. Jiu.
미안해요, 아가씨. 지우.
I sprained my hand while cutting firewood recently .
최근 장작을 자르다가 손을 삐었습니다 .
Gui has been cooking these days.
요즘 구이가 요리를 하고 있어요.
I can't help you.
나는 당신을 도울 수 없습니다.
Better to ask someone else.
다른 사람에게 물어보는 것이 더 좋습니다.
The strange woman you mentioned is right here.
당신이 말한 이상한 여자가 바로 여기 있어요.
here. Right here.
여기. 바로 여기에.
She looks older, but she's pregnant.
그녀는 나이가 많아 보이지만 임신 중입니다.
So is she a demon?
그럼 그 사람은 악마인가요?
must.
해야 하다.
this.
이것.
How embarrassing!
정말 당황스럽네요!
let's go.
갑시다.
Master, let me do it.
선생님, 제가 할게요.
I added something
뭔가를 추가했어요
from brochure
브로셔에서
no tea
차 없음
Let a beautiful and smart person
아름답고 똑똑한 사람을 보자
As long as I can follow it.
내가 따라갈 수 있는 한.
If one day I die
어느 날 내가 죽는다면
Head to Wuhua Mountain.
Wuhua Mountain으로 향하세요.
Monte Wuhua?
몬테 우후아?
I want to go to Wuhua Mountain as soon as possible.
하루빨리 우화산에 가보고 싶습니다.
lady.
숙녀.
Miss. Jiuling is...
놓치다. 지울링은...
you!
너!
lady.
숙녀.
If you can save her and the baby
그녀와 아기를 구할 수 있다면
I'd love to go
나는 가고 싶다
Everything you do is rewarded.
당신이 하는 모든 일은 보상을 받습니다.
Only one of my disciples could be so stupid!
내 제자 중 단 한 명만이 이렇게 멍청할 수 있어요!
She sacrificed her life just to keep him alive.
그녀는 그를 살리기 위해 자신의 목숨을 희생했습니다.
lady.
숙녀.
Pipa Mouth can only be used once.
비파 입은 한 번만 사용할 수 있습니다.
There's no point in me killing you.
내가 당신을 죽이는 것은 아무 소용이 없습니다.
No...
아니요...
Is he sure?
그 사람이 확실한가요?
explain.
설명하다.
If I can't save them both
둘 다 구할 수 없다면
Who will choose?
누가 선택할 것인가?
lady.
숙녀.
if you can save her
당신이 그녀를 구할 수 있다면
I can accept not having children.
나는 아이가 없다는 것을 받아들일 수 있다.
As long as He Jiuling is by my side.
He Jiuling이 내 곁에 있는 한.
Even if she is no longer young and beautiful?
그녀가 더 이상 젊고 아름답지 않더라도 ?
Em Nanjiang,
엠 난장(Em Nanjiang),
I once told a story about a swordsman.
언젠가 어느 검객에 관한 이야기를 한 적이 있다.
That female swordsman
그 여자 검객
That's my mother.
그 분은 우리 어머니예요.
My father exchanged letters with her
아버지는 그녀와 편지를 주고받았어요
Gradually, they fall in love.
점차적으로 그들은 사랑에 빠진다.
Even if the result is guaranteed,
결과가 보장되더라도
He was worried.
그는 걱정했다.
Then,
그 다음에,
He no longer guesses
그는 더 이상 추측하지 않습니다
or reply to her letter,
아니면 그녀의 편지에 답장을 보내거나,
Because my father went to find her.
아버지가 그녀를 찾으러 갔기 때문이다.
and married her.
그리고 그녀와 결혼했습니다.
He wants to be with her in every battle
그는 모든 전투에서 그녀와 함께하고 싶어
And follow it day in and day out.
그리고 매일 그것을 따르십시오.
He is a prophet himself
그 자체가 선지자다
And her peace charm.
그리고 그녀의 평화의 매력.
Then,
그 다음에,
Just like you asked me before
아까 물어보셨던 것처럼
Regarding whether He Jiuling lost or died,
He Jiuling의 패배 또는 사망 여부에 대해
if you ask me now
지금 나한테 묻는다면
If she is old and not beautiful
만약 그 사람이 늙어서 아름답지 않다면
What will I do? my answer
나는 무엇을 할 것인가? 내 대답
It will always be the same as my dad's.
그것은 언제나 우리 아버지의 것과 같을 것이다.
Even if death separates us, I will spend my life with her .
죽음이 우리를 갈라놓더라도 나는 그녀와 함께 평생을 보낼 것입니다 .
Quando fui a Nanjiang,
Quando fui a Nanjiang,
I'm ready.
난 준비됐어.
She protects her homeland and her motherland
그녀는 조국과 조국을 보호합니다
I will protect her.
나는 그녀를 보호할 것이다.
Quickly.
빠르게.
We're almost there.
거의 다 왔어.
- Is Jiuling here? - Yes.
- 지우링이 여기 있어요? - 예.
- go. - Show the way.
- 가다. - 길을 보여주세요.
teacher.
선생님.
Is that you?
당신인가요?
if not me
내가 아니라면
Who else would take your body?
또 누가 당신의 몸을 가져갈까요?
what are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Now
지금
Now is not the time for chatting.
지금은 잡담할 때가 아니다.
looking at you.
너를보고있는.
It's only been a few months since we met
만난지 몇달밖에 안됐는데
and destroyed his body.
그리고 그의 몸을 파괴했습니다.
I spoke to you in Nanjiang.
나는 난장에서 당신과 이야기를 나눴습니다.
He relies on his pipa mouth to survive.
그는 생존을 위해 비파 입에 의존합니다.
How can you give up?
어떻게 포기할 수 있나요?
If something happens to you,
당신에게 무슨 일이 생기면,
like me...
나처럼...
what can I do?
어떡해?
teacher.
선생님.
You know everything.
넌 다 아는군.
baby.
아기.
I have no choice.
어쩔수없이.
I am very nervous.
나는 매우 긴장된다.
I can not....
난 못해....
I couldn't just watch him walk away and do nothing.
나는 그가 아무것도 하지 않고 떠나는 것을 보고만 있을 수 없었다.
Really sorry.
정말 미안해요.
You say you're sorry
당신은 미안하다고 말해요
But if I had to choose again
하지만 다시 선택해야 한다면
You will do the same.
당신도 똑같이 할 것입니다.
men in this world
이 세상의 남자들
They are not good.
그들은 좋지 않습니다.
after you die,
당신이 죽은 후에,
He will remember you for a while
그 사람은 당신을 한동안 기억할 거예요
But not forever.
그러나 영원히는 아닙니다.
When all you have left is a skeleton
당신에게 남은 것은 해골뿐일 때
He lived a happy and carefree life.
그는 행복하고 근심 걱정 없는 삶을 살았습니다.
I'd rather you didn't remember me at all.
차라리 당신이 나를 전혀 기억하지 않았으면 좋겠어요.
you.
너.
He can be carefree and happy,
그는 평온하고 행복할 수 있습니다.
Feliz
펠리즈
And fall in love with someone else.
그리고 다른 사람과 사랑에 빠지세요.
As long as he is happy
그 사람이 행복하다면
everything will be fine.
다 괜찮을거야.
you are too naive.
당신은 너무 순진해요.
You are so stupid.
당신은 정말 바보입니다.
I have been stupid all my life.
나는 평생 동안 바보였습니다.
I accept.
동의 함.
There is no turning back in life.
인생에는 되돌릴 수 없습니다.
We must move on.
우리는 계속 나아가야 합니다.
I don't have much time.
시간이 별로 없어요.
The only thing I won't let go
내가 놓지 않을 유일한 것
This is the baby in my belly.
내 뱃속에 있는 아기입니다.
He is very strong.
그는 매우 강하다.
He has been with me until now
그 사람은 지금까지 나와 함께 해왔다.
On a difficult journey,
힘든 여정 속에서,
But he's still here.
하지만 그는 아직 여기 있어요.
He is indeed a miracle.
그는 참으로 기적입니다.
He needs the desire to open his eyes
그에게는 눈을 뜨고 싶은 욕구가 필요하다
and see the world.
그리고 세상을 보세요.
I have nothing
나는 아무것도 없다
Unless you find a way to save him.
그를 구할 방법을 찾지 않는 한 .
This is truly a miracle.
이것은 정말 기적입니다.
Maybe this time,
아마도 이번에는,
A miracle could save him.
기적이 그를 구할 수 있었습니다.
There is no Pipa Zui in his body.
그의 몸에는 Pipa Zui가 없습니다.
But it may still be there in him.
그러나 그것은 여전히 ​​그 사람 안에 있을 수 있습니다.
You said he walked with you through a difficult road,
힘든 길을 함께 걸어갔다고 하더군요 .
He's still here.
그는 아직 여기 있어요.
Have you ever thought that it might be because of Pipa Mouth?
비파입 때문 이 아닐까 생각해본 적 있으신가요 ?
Based on your current physical condition,
현재 고객님의 신체상태를 토대로
I can only ask them to find you as soon as possible.
가능한 한 빨리 당신을 찾아달라고 부탁할 수밖에 없습니다 .
and try to find ways
그리고 방법을 찾으려고 노력해 보세요
Extract the remaining Pipazui
남은 피파주이를 추출하세요
his body.
그의 몸.
I don't want him to go through this pain.
나는 그가 이런 고통을 겪는 것을 원하지 않습니다 .
Ling.
링.
He grew up with Pipa Zui.
그는 Pipa Zui와 함께 자랐습니다.
In fact, that's how I survived
사실 그래서 살아남았어
she let him
그녀는 그에게 허락했다
Being different from others.
다른 사람들과 다르다.
He even picked the pipa mouth
심지어 비파 입을 골랐다.
your body,
너의 몸,
He doesn't feel pain like other people do.
그는 다른 사람들처럼 고통을 느끼지 않습니다.
That's no problem.
그건 문제가 되지 않습니다.
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
I only read one sentence
한 문장만 읽었는데
Records about such persons
그러한 사람에 관한 기록
My master’s master from Mount Wuhua.
Wuhua 산의 나의 주인의 주인.
He is a miracle.
그는 기적입니다.
Believe me.
나를 믿어.
Go to the drugstore to buy me ginseng and angelica. quickly.
약국에 가서 인삼과 안젤리카를 사주세요. 빠르게.
Sim.
심.
here.
여기.
healthy?
건강한?
Clear.
분명한.
let's go.
갑시다.
Shangyuan, TianTing, Palácio Taiwei.
Shangyuan, TianTing, Palácio Taiwei.
Dazzling stellar phenomena light up the sky.
눈부신 별 현상이 하늘을 밝게 비춥니다.
Dazzling stellar phenomena persist in the sky.
눈부신 별 현상이 하늘에 지속됩니다.
Duanmen is just one of the city gates.
Duanmen은 성문 중 하나 일뿐입니다.
The guards are divided into east and west.
경비병은 동쪽과 서쪽으로 나누어져 있습니다.
Teacher, I have a question here.
선생님, 여기서 질문이 있습니다.
This is not the time for questions.
지금은 질문할 시간이 아닙니다.
If you have questions,
질문이 있으시면,
You still don’t understand after I’ve finished speaking.
내가 말을 마친 후에도 당신은 아직도 이해하지 못합니다.
You can ask them.
그들에게 물어볼 수 있습니다.
Now ask them the same thing.
이제 그들에게도 똑같은 질문을 해보세요.
Because I never understand
난 절대 이해하지 못하니까
I am excited.
나는 흥분된다.
Speaking of which, about the guards.
말하자면 경비원에 관한 것입니다.
Where are your manners?
당신의 매너는 어디에 있습니까?
as a psychic
심령술사로서
you shouldn't worry
걱정하지 않아도 돼
Or lack of patience for success.
또는 성공에 대한 인내심이 부족합니다.
- Master. - Must remain calm and tranquil at all times.
- 주인. - 항상 침착하고 평온한 상태를 유지해야 합니다.
Just like our master.
우리 주인님과 똑같습니다.
Just like the master, sometimes he gets impatient
주인님처럼 가끔 초조해할 때도 있어요
It's also normal.
그것은 또한 정상입니다.
Master, hurry up.
선생님, 서두르세요.
How did you get in?
어떻게 들어왔나요?
I still haven't forgiven him. leave.
나는 아직도 그를 용서하지 않았습니다. 떠나다.
Madam, just let me wait here today.
부인, 오늘은 여기서 기다리게 해주세요.
Go away, you make me sick.
가세요. 당신 때문에 마음이 아프네요.
lady.
숙녀.
skirt.
치마.
Okay, I'll go right away.
알았어, 바로 갈게.
It's daybreak.
새벽이다.
Why is there no movement inside?
왜 안에서 움직임이 없나요?
Master.
주인.
They're gone.
그들은 사라졌습니다.
Master, they went out through the side door.
선생님, 옆문으로 나갔어요.
Master.
주인.
After years of entanglement,
수년간의 얽힌 끝에,
I think you understand the meaning of "deep affection".
'깊은 애정'의 의미를 아실 것 같은데요 .
He Jiuling was fine.
He Jiuling은 괜찮았습니다.
I'll take her there.
내가 그녀를 거기로 데려갈게요.
I just want you two
난 단지 너희 둘을 원해
Say goodbye and forget.
작별 인사를 하고 잊어버리세요.
look.
바라보다.
Want tone.
톤을 원합니다.
Everyone says that the water cities in the south are beautiful.
모두가 남쪽의 물 도시가 아름답다고 말합니다 .
The excitement and prosperity here
이곳의 설렘과 번영
No less than the capital.
자본보다 적지 않습니다.
Shall we go to Liuzhou tomorrow?
내일 류저우로 갈까요?
Your Majesty, it’s not Liuzhou, it’s Chu.
폐하, 류저우가 아니라 추입니다.
Why Trudy? Who organized this?
왜 트루디인가? 누가 이걸 조직했나요?
The princess learned that Your Majesty wanted to visit secretly,
공주는 폐하께서 몰래 방문하고 싶어하신다 는 것을 알고
and wrote to invite us.
그리고 우리를 초대하기 위해 편지를 썼습니다.
No, we won't.
아니요, 그렇지 않습니다.
Chu planned torture
추는 고문을 계획했다
These courtiers followed me.
이 신하들이 나를 따라왔습니다.
Yes, I will inform others and change the route to Liuzhou today.
네, 오늘 다른 사람들에게 알리고 류저우로 경로를 변경하겠습니다.
look.
바라보다.
This is for you.
이건 널위한거야.
Chu Chu may be a bit rebellious,
츄츄는 좀 반항적일 수도 있지만,
But what she said was not wrong.
하지만 그녀의 말은 틀리지 않았다.
southern women
남부 여성
more enthusiastic and fun
더 열정적이고 재미있게
There are more women than there are in the capital.
수도에 있는 것보다 여성이 더 많습니다.
Little uncle.
작은 삼촌.
Can I ask you a favor?
부탁 하나 해도 될까요?
Do you call me uncle?
나를 삼촌이라고 부르나요?
uncle.
삼촌.
Can you help me?
도와주세요?
No, uncle. I...
아뇨, 삼촌. 나...
If you insist on a title, just call me brother.
굳이 직함을 고집한다면 형이라고 불러주세요.
All the best bro.
최선을 다하세요.
All is well in the South.
남부에서는 모든 것이 잘되고 있습니다.
Except for the children,
아이들을 제외하고,
A bit stupider than the people in the capital.
수도에 사는 사람들보다 조금 더 멍청합니다.
Tell me, what do you need?
말해 보세요. 무엇이 필요합니까?
Can you help me load this?
이거 로드하는 걸 도와주실 수 있나요?
We are still far from my home
우리 집은 아직 멀다
I can no longer carry it.
더 이상 가지고 다닐 수가 없어요.
Why are you still here at your age?
왜 아직도 그 나이에 여기 계시나요?
Where are your parents?
부모님은 어디에 계시나요?
Why are you asking my family?
왜 우리 가족에게 물어보나요?
I'm just asking.
그냥 물어보는 거야
You shouldn't have told me.
나한테 말하지 말았어야 했는데.
So young, if you meet a bad person
너무 어려서 나쁜 사람 만나면
This can be dangerous.
이는 위험할 수 있습니다.
Bad guy?
나쁜 사람?
I'm not afraid of bad people.
나는 나쁜 사람들을 두려워하지 않습니다.
Why aren't you afraid?
왜 두려워하지 않습니까?
You are just a girl.
당신은 단지 소녀입니다.
Aren't you afraid that I will kidnap you?
내가 당신을 납치할까 두렵지 않나요?
I want to see him try.
나는 그가 시도하는 것을 보고 싶다.
You are strong, aren't you?
당신은 강하지 않나요?
No, I am the weakest in the family.
아니요, 저는 가족 중 가장 약합니다.
Wang Dequan, this young lady may be a bit stupid.
왕더취안(Wang Dequan), 이 아가씨는 좀 멍청한 것 같아요.
But she's funny.
하지만 그녀는 재밌어요.
Sim.
심.
let's go. I carry.
갑시다. 나는 가지고 다닌다.
Take it.
가져.
Okay, let's go.
좋아, 가자.
What is here?
여기에 무엇이 있습니까?
There is noise.
소음이 있습니다.
A cricket?
귀뚜라미?
No.
아니요.
Scarab?
풍뎅이?
But that doesn't seem to be the case.
그러나 그것은 사실이 아닌 것 같습니다.
An owl?
올빼미?
Are there such insects around you?
주변에 그런 벌레가 있나요?
No.
아니요.
My mother said I was the only one who could raise him.
어머니는 그 아이를 키울 수 있는 사람은 나뿐이라고 말씀하셨다.
Don't open it.
열지 마세요.
Now you believe me, don't you?
이제 당신은 내 말을 믿습니까?
I'm not afraid of bad people.
나는 나쁜 사람들을 두려워하지 않습니다.
It seems that he has drank a hundred bottles of wine.
그는 와인을 백 병 정도 마신 것 같습니다.
Go away. go out.
저리 가요. 나가.
I'm not afraid of bad people.
나는 나쁜 사람들을 두려워하지 않습니다.
I am not a bad guy.
나는 나쁜 사람이 아닙니다.
This is not my intention.
이것은 내 의도가 아닙니다.
Mother.
어머니.
Ronger,
론저,
let's go.
갑시다.
Where is my daughter?
내 딸은 어디에 있나요?
Boss, are you okay?
사장님, 괜찮으세요?
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
♫ You have been waiting for me for a long time. ♫
♫ 당신은 오랫동안 나를 기다려왔습니다. ♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I gently push the sitar away, waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 시타르를 살며시 밀어내며 당신 같은 사람을 기다리며♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫
♫ Under the sunset♫
♫ 석양 아래♫
♫I traveled thousands of miles♫
♫나는 수천 마일을 여행했어요♫
♫ Play the sitar under the moonlight ♫
♫ 달빛 아래서 시타르를 연주해 보세요 ♫
♫ Drinks won’t let me forget ♫
♫ 술은 내가 잊지 못하게 해줄 거예요 ♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀 있어요♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫ You turn around silently and close the wedding book♫
♫ 당신은 조용히 돌아서서 결혼식 장부를 덮습니다♫
♫Ask how many stars there are in the sky♫
♫하늘에 별이 몇 개 있는지 물어보세요♫
♫I write to you about my desire♫
♫내 소망에 관해 당신에게 편지를 씁니다♫
♫Our destiny is written on paper♫
♫우리의 운명은 종이에 적혀 있어요♫
♫ Like the strongest wine ♫
♫ 가장 강한 포도주처럼 ♫
♫ There is no escape from fate ♫
♫ 운명에는 탈출구가 없습니다 ♫
♫Looking back I see you waiting♫
♫돌아보면 기다리고 있는 네가 보여♫
♫Our lives are full of joy and sadness♫
♫우리 삶은 기쁨과 슬픔 으로 가득 차 있습니다 ♫
♫ Desire crystallizes into shining stars♫
♫ 욕망은 빛나는 별들로 결정화됩니다♫
♫I play the sitar gently, waiting for someone like you♫
♫나는 시타르를 부드럽게 연주하며 당신 같은 사람을 기다리고 있어요♫
♫In the end you are my inevitable destiny♫
♫결국 당신은 나의 피할 수 없는 운명♫